|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
Is this alchemy of souls?
Is my soul moving now?
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee
The soul has not moved
What happened?
Chan Wook
Chan Wook!
Kil Joo, you switched bodies with my student
Moo Deok
I was weak to protect him from you
But I will definitely finish you off
I didn't know
why were you so worried about Chan Wook?
Shut up!
Teacher!
It's me, Chan Wook
We haven't changed
Look into my eyes
It's me
The only one who can look at you from such a distance
Do you recognize me?
He's got a mark on his shoulder
His soul apparently returned back to his body
Then why am I okay?
Not really
You have changed too. Look
You don't have a bracelet on, but your hand doesn't tremble
You're right. I can move it freely
The reflector helped gain energy
Poison opened your gates, reflect increased energy
Chan Wook, you are incredibly lucky
I'm sure I saw you there
What?
Why?
Why are you okay?
You didn't succeed because of your weak energy.
You are also a nomad
Nak Soo you too
you will petrify and die
Like me
Like your father
My father?
Yes
Stargazer Mage
Cho Chun!
My father...
was he a nomad?
It wasn't Daeho's main families who killed your family.
It was your father. He turned into a soul swallower and killed everyone
Stay inside and don't go out
If you see your father, run
Don't let him catch you
Both you and your father were used
You will turn to stone and die
My father was a nomad
did Dan Zhu?
Jin Moo from Jeonbugwan?
Jin Moo is not the real Dan Joo
True Dan Zhu is someone else
- And who is this?
- Real
can stop petrification
Because he has an ice stone
Who is the real Dan Zhu?
Moo Deok, are you okay?
Normal
Run after him. Faster!
We need to get out of here
until the poison from witchcraft spread
View everything
- Yes
Nobody
I felt the energy of witchcraft
Master Huo was right. This sapsari is Gwigu
Did they really perform alchemy of souls here?
What is this?
Lying on the ground
Maybe it's a reflector
This bracelet...
Is this Mr. Chang Wook's bracelet?
Why is he here?
So Uk was here?
They fought
Do you think something happened to him?
Return to Sosnovy Bor and report what you saw
Dan Gu, come and look for Wook
- I'll look in the area
- Okay
How did the magicians of Sosnovy Bor find out?
You are also a nomad
Nak Soo, you too
you will petrify and die
Like me
Like your father
Father...
Both you and your father
used. You'll turn to stone
and you will die
Why?
Why you again?
Is this a nomad?
No, maid Uka
I accidentally wounded her, I need to take her to the doctors
What a day this is
Trade was going well
I need to replenish my energy, otherwise I’ll completely petrify
-Have you finished?
- That's it already
Shall we have a drink?
- Okay
- Faster
Let's go
I can't come back if I make a fuss
I need to find a quiet place where I can get enough
Move away
Oh, oh, come on in
Mister
You won't fool us with these tricks
You've been following her since you entered the capital
This man is stalking us
You followed her all the way to the inn
We were just in one direction
Don't lie
You were staring at her the whole time!
Not at all
Song Yi
Don't embarrass him
I felt uncomfortable that you were following me, and it was also rude on your part
If you don't want me to look for another inn,
go away
girl
Why did you decide that I was following you?
You don't owe me anything
I don’t even know you, why should I follow you?
- Because she's very...
- Shut up, Sun Yi
Let her answer
I had a lot of problems because of men who followed me because of my beauty
So I decided
that you are one of them
I see
But that's not true
The beauty was not impressive
And I didn't follow you
Well then,
I'm sorry
Can I go up then?
- Mrs. Ho
- Yes?
you must eat
This bastard...
That is...
Are you embarrassed because you might cross paths with him again?
No
I just don't feel good
Change into dry clothes
I'll bring you some porridge
Are you okay?
What was that?
Have you been following him?
Yes
Glad you weren't hurt
Wait a minute
Thank you
If you don't feel well,
go to Sejukwon in Sosnovy Bor
Do you know about Saejukwon?
I'm from Saejukwon...
I am Ho Young Ok
Instead of a friend nearby, you have a whistle
It means your friend left you
Did you know
who am I all this time
Are you okay?
Hey, how are you there?
Try to get up. Slowly
Monster!
Soul swallower!
It's a soul swallower!
- Soul Swallower
- Soul swallower!
True Dan Zhu is someone else
The real one can stop petrification
Yes, go to your Dan Zhu
Is Kil Ju missing?
We don't know where he is since he went after Chan Wook's maid
Chan Wook's maid?
Why does he need her?
To be honest, he was following Chan Wook
The spirit amulet that Nak Soo left behind belonged to Chan Wook
He probably thought that Chan Wook was somehow related to her
You should have told me earlier!
He says to be silent
Probably wanted to find hard evidence
Tell all the mages to find Kil Ju
Chan Wook's bracelet
found where they performed the alchemy of souls?
Dan Gu is looking for Mr.
Master So inspects the surroundings of the temple
- They were in the temple?
- Yes
I doubt Uk is capable of alchemy
Master Li,
What if someone’s soul migrated into Uka’s body?
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine
She will protect him
Where is
our leader, when is there such chaos here?
Before Uk was born...
20 years ago...
Chang Gang
performed alchemy of souls?
Gwangju Jeonbugwan and witchcraft?
This is just funny!
Jin Moo told me about this
I didn't dare ask him
that's why I came to you
Mrs. Do Hwa
I was worried that Gwangju
became interested in some strange spells
But it didn't last long
Gwangju hasn't been home for a year
Trained spells with Jin Moo in Jeonbugwan's secret room
But
he stopped when his wife got pregnant
He is the son of the deceased king
King
died due to illness without being able to move
How is this possible?
This is possible due to the alchemy of souls
Being a magician
he was burning with a simple interest in such things
No
He committed
something irreparable
with the lives of Do Hwa and Wook
The magician from Jeonjingak is urgently looking for our master
Didn't know you were here, uncle
What is it?
I think
Uk fell victim to the alchemy of souls
What?
This is Jeonbugwan
Is the real Dan Zhu behind these walls?
This is the road to the palace
Is the real Dan Zhu there?
I'm from Jeonbugwan
It's probably urgent
Show your face
It's urgent. Out of the way
Show me your face first
Soul Swallower
Behind him
Real in the palace
Ice stone, right?
You mentioned him
I will find him and save her from a similar fate to you.
Wait, he...
Look
Is he really dead?
- Touch it
- Is it worth it?
He tried to get into the palace until he turned to stone
Did you kill him?
How dare we?
Suddenly some unknown magician appeared and killed him
What family is he from? Have you seen the face?
No, it was hidden
But I saw what he used
It was Tansu
- Tansu?
- Yes, I'm sure
He hit with energy from the sword
Tansu was owned by Nak Su
Was there someone else who mastered it?
I heard you caught a soul swallower
We came to see who it is
Of course. You can look
This is Kil Ju
one of your people
That's right
Bring in the body and get everyone out
Yes
Jin Mu was with me when they performed alchemy
He's confused too
He didn't know they had done alchemy
I'll take care of it since everything happened in Jeonbugwan.
Has nothing to do with Sosnovy Bor
Of course
If necessary, we will provide assistance
If necessary
Another nomad turned into a souleater?
Fortunately, he was caught and killed
And who was it?
Kil Ju,
magician of Jeonbugwan
Has Kil Ju become a nomad?
Did Jeongbugwan catch him?
He was caught in front of the palace
He tried to get into the palace when he was running wild
Did he come here?
Suddenly a magician appeared
who used Tansu
And who was it?
Kil Joo killed Nak Soo
- What?
- Nak Soo?
She's back!
- Mercenary?
A magician wielding Tansu who appeared in front of the palace
Nak Su owned it
- Really?
- Amazing
- Was it her?
- She?
Wait a minute
Nak Soo is dead
Exactly!
Everyone here saw her body burned.
I saw it myself
- Yes
- Exactly
The body is burned, but the soul is alive
The shadow warrior has become a nomad!
- What?
- Is it true?
- It can’t be
- Seriously?
But Nak Soo is a girl
And Kil Ju was killed by a young man
Tall young man in blue robe
Nak Su is a nomad, right?
She could have migrated into the body of this young man
And then I became stronger
She was strong
But in a man’s body she became even stronger
Killing Kil Joo is her revenge
Jeonbugwan for the burned body
and killing her people
Why should we take revenge?
Pine Forest killed Nak Su
"Dressed in blue, the incredible Nak Soo is back"
"Pine Forest is her next goal"
These are the rumors going around
The soul swallower was caught just a couple of hours ago
and already such absurd rumors?
Rumors like these are as fast as wildfire.
And the rumors are not groundless
The magician used Tansa,
like Nak Soo
Was she the only one who owned it?
I would like to, I’ve mastered it right now
If these rumors spread throughout Sosnovy Bor,
you will answer. Make sure this doesn't happen
Yes
What a blessing that you became a soul swallower
not young master
But why did we find his bracelet there?
We'll find out when we find him
You look bad
You should
go home and wait for him there
Are you feeling unwell?
I was so surprised that the honey cookies I ate yesterday
still in my throat
I was so scared when I heard about the soul swallower,
that the soul first left the body and then returned
Is it really back?
Is that you, maid Kim?
No, head. I'm Pak's maid
I could have hit the young gentleman on the back, which scares me so much
Hit me instead
I give permission to Maid Pak
Come on
My hands are strong
It will hurt
I won't cry
hit
Consider that you've already hit me once
Why?
Will you do something unpleasant to me in return?
Then I'll cancel this blow
Hit me too
Come on
Hurry
I...
I don't want to hurt you
As the head of Sosnovy Bor,
I'll have to act cold and heartless
But I really
I don't want to hurt you
Are you worried about
What did they ask me yesterday about Master Chang Gan?
A lot has happened
Being the head, I couldn't
be objective
Your blow brought me to my senses
Now we must act wisely
Feel free to hit me
as Pak's maid
From you
I'll accept
Why are you here?
Master Ho said to find out where the witchcraft is coming from
And on the spot I found this
Apparently lost
Don't you need him anymore?
No, not anymore
Almost lost the Jin family's treasure
Thanks for finding it
You've lost something else
Aren't you going to look for Moo Deok?
Where is she?
I found her when she was hiding in the forest
She was wounded and bleeding
Moo Deok
owner,
how could you leave me?
What?
You ran away leaving me
Play along with me
Yes... I ran away
Exactly!
We encountered a soul swallower while hiding from the rain
Thanks to you
This soul eater almost ate me
I'm sorry
I was so scared that I couldn't think about anything, and I ran away
Yul mistook Moo Deok for a soul swallower and almost killed him
If he hadn't taken care of her properly, Moo Deok would have died.
Yul,
thank you for saving Moo Deok and taking care of her
Did you really run away and leave her?
Otherwise I would die
Sometimes you only have to think about yourself
What are you looking at? Don't agree?
In any case, I'm glad
that we're both fine
Yes
I heard you were hiding in Danhyangok
Did you hear what our leader said?
Sosnovy Bor will take your shame upon itself
I'm so tired of it
Why, if I’m not even a member of Sosnovy Bor?
Duel with the prince in two weeks
Stay out of town until then, don't cause problems.
Keep your head down
Thank you for taking care of me
Apparently, Uk copes well without a bracelet
I think he can control the energy now
He risked his life again and got what he wanted
And you were there again
If you cared that much, you would have left me to die.
Maybe
next time
Moo Deok
I'm coming, master
We went
Uk was not injured
That's good
He saw
who was with Kil-ju when he changed souls?
Probably the guy in blue
Wook was too busy running to look
Did you ask his maid?
She must have seen the spells
Moo Deok...
If she saw it, she hardly knows what it is
This is an ordinary maid who knows little about magic
What about the hand?
Got hurt?
The reflector I touched still contains poison from witchcraft.
But I'm fine
I'll go
Why did you want to see me?
I heard you took my wedding gifts
Why?
Were you afraid that I would destroy them?
I'll save them for your next wedding
Throw them away
Marriage is no longer my priority
Don't be so embarrassed
The wedding was prepared secretly, few people knew about it
Really?
Cho Young!
They say you're getting married
I heard about gifts, and that I found a craftsman to make rings
Apparently the rumors have spread
Congratulations
Congratulations, Young Master Park
- Me?
- I know that you are getting married
He received gifts
I went with you to try on rings
Really?
There were absurd rumors that you were marrying Chan Wook
No?
It's you two getting married
Yes, that's right
But don't talk about it
Still a secret
Okay
See you
I told you it's Dan Gu
Exactly. She's not crazy to marry Uka again
Don't tell
Dan Gu
Why did you confirm their words?
It's better than admitting that Wook rejected you twice
Let's say that this time you refused to marry me
It will still be just rumors
Do you agree to this arrangement?
You'll be embarrassed
I agree
Won Moo Deok?
Are you back here again? Weren't you hurt?
What?
Forget. Move away
Looking for Moo Deok again?
No. The dress just looked familiar
Moo Deok sold it to us
- Did you sell it?
- Yes
She said it was a gift from a frivolous man
And also that he is well off
and won't ask for the dress back
Did she really say that?
Yes. Stink Moo Deok and silk can't go hand in hand
Watch your language
What?
I gave her this name and only I can call her that
Not you
Sorry
And also
she looked good in that dress
Better than you in that blue cape
Apparently you don't like it
What is this?
Everyone here is like this
This is Nak Soo's robe
Whose?
Nomad Nak Su killed the magician Jeonbugwan in front of the palace
She was wearing a similar robe
Now everyone in the capital has this
- Come, buy Nak Su’s robe
- I have one
It will protect your soul from being consumed
- This one
- Take
I need this one
- Nak Su's Cape
- Try it on
Nomad in Blue
Everyone thinks Nak Soo is back from the dead
But thanks to "Nak Soo in Blue",
no one remembers the fight between Uka and the prince
I wonder where Wook and Moo Deok are
They weren't in Danhyangok
I'm sure they're fine
They'll be back in two weeks
By the way, Yul
I bought it for myself too. Do you want to try it on?
Okay
Who could it be?
Nak Soo in blue, wielding Tansu?
You said this was the grave of the soulswallowers
So he must be here
Your father
Baby
I thought he was killed by the magicians of the four families
Jin Mu took me in, I called him Dan Zhu
But...
my father was a nomad, he was used
And I was used, then abandoned
As Kil Joo said,
I will petrify and die
When I'm petrified
will you bury me here?
I found out where the real Dan Zhu is
In the palace. The real one is there
Tell me about the ice stone
Are you sure
that he was destroyed
by Master Seo Kyung and the head of Jinyeowon 200 years ago?
We are sure that he
not in Sosnovy Bor
Hello Dan Zhu
Kil Ju wanted an ice stone, so he came to the palace to see me
I didn't know
that Kil Joo knows who the real Dan Joo is
The day the Choi family regains power
and Sosnovy Bor, the cause of our fall, was destroyed
It's already very close. Then I will begin to rule in Daeho
I look forward to this day no less than you
We must find and kill the one who dealt with Kil Ju
This man must have been waiting for Kil Joo
will come to the palace for the stone
If he knows where the stone is,
you have to find
and kill him
I don't know who it is
but the real Dan Zhu is in the palace and he has a stone
With its help, nomads do not turn into soulswallowers
So, we need to get into the palace and find Dan Zhu?
It's impossible now
I am a weak magician rejected by Jeongjingak
But I will climb forward
And I will definitely get to the palace
teacher,
I'll find
stone for you
Chan Wook
Your teacher is not strong enough to pull you up
or cover from behind
You've never been like this
Always pushed me to death
But after each time I became better and stronger than I was
Keep putting me in danger
The main thing is to be close
Okay
I'll be there and push you to death,
if you stop
I'll find Uka and make sure he doesn't show up for the fight.
No need
If he wants to come,
let him
This is an official duel between magicians
We won't be able to intervene even if one dies.
If someone dies
so that's how it will be
Won't you stop this?
The unified council demanded from Uka
fight on behalf of Sosnovy Bor
Run away from cowardly
and will die with honor,
I will just watch how the head of Sosnovy Bor
Their Lordships the King and Queen have arrived
A month ago, Go Won, heir to the Daeho royal family,
challenged the eldest son of the Chan family to a duel
Sosnovy Bor accepted the challenge on behalf of Chan Wook
By signing this document,
you undertake not to make any claims
even in the event of someone's death
The match will begin at noon
If Chang Wook doesn't show up by then,
we'll take this as defeat
You should mention the punishment he will receive if he doesn't show up
If Chang Wook doesn't come today,
he will lose the right to become the next Gwangju
Jeonbugwana
To me
What's in those jugs?
Water
Water?
Chapter, it's already noon
Close the hall door
I have to
announce his loss
Close
Chan Wook has arrived!
Mister...
Mister
Everything will be fine
Chan Wook
You signed the paper
Now no one will interfere
even if you die during the fight
Got it
Mother,
stop this fight
He will die by the hand of the Crown Prince
He came because he was ready to die
Your marriage is annulled again
His fate has nothing to do with us
You can start
First: don't attack, just defend
You attack him with your skills -
you'll die
You can only attack when he
will lose concentration
I'm sure he arranged them
Can you really go to Sosnovy Bor whenever you want?
Yes. And what?
I have a favor to ask
You can place water in the training room,
so he can use Tansu?
These water jugs confuse me
Break them down
Owner
Tansu
Prince...
Duel
finished
Not fair. Doesn't count!
It was Tansu
It can only be mastered by those who have mastered Chisa
How could Chang Wook, whose gate was only recently opened, take possession of him?
I'm sure
that one of the masters helped him
How would they help him?
if everyone was watching?
Don't talk nonsense!
Chan Wook, answer
You really mastered Chisa and then Tansa
in such a short time?
Not really
I have trouble controlling my energy
I can only use Tansa if there is water.
I only know how to cut water
Who taught you this?
Someone should have helped you
Nobody
You look
This is just funny
Claims to have mastered this skill himself
I noticed jugs of water here
Who installed them?
Your teacher?
I studied on my own
I won't fall for this!
Chan Wook, explain yourself
Who helped you train?
I put the jugs
And I was with him
Everything he said is true
Who are you?
How dare you interfere?
Shut up!
This is Hemp Master Li
Master So Kyung's student
Say hello to him!
Hello master
I was with him in Danhyangok and saw everything
He learned to chop drops of water for days on end.
And with him
there was only his maid
Master Li vouched for him
Are there any other objections?
Let's go, Your Majesty
Let Chan Wook enter Jeonbugwan
No wonder Gwangju Chang Gang's son is so talented
Since you don't have a teacher yet, Jeonbugwan will gladly accept you
I don't need it here!
I should be his teacher
I opened his gates, and it was I who gave him my energy
Wook, come with me to Sejukwon
I'll teach you everything I know
Or maybe to Jinyeowon?
Engagement with Cho Young is broken,
but we will consider you family and teach you our spells
Chan Wook,
if you want, you can join Jeonjingak
We will accept you
Moo Deok,
Everyone calls me. Where to go?
Enter Sosnovy Bor,
owner
I, Chan Wook, the eldest son of the Chan family,
I will enter Jeonjingak
Thanks for watching with us!
Alchemy
Shower
The master became the magician of Jeonjingak
Welcome our new magician Chan Wook
I hate your master until I grind my teeth
Of course
If this love is so fickle, then I don’t need it!
Let me in
Moo Deok
I should be with the owner
Go home, wait there
Mister Chan got out and went home
Master! Wait there
- I'm coming to you
- I found questions for the exam
Whatever happens
I will go to Sosnovy Bor to the owner
Moo Deok
I can handle anything just to see you